<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="prayers_array">
        <item>Thank God for what He has done for you this year.</item>
        <item>Let frustration and disappointment, be the portion of every object fashioned against my life and family, in the name of Jesus.</item>
        <item>Every tie to polluted objects and items between my life and family, break, in the name of Jesus.</item>
        <item>Every unspoken curse against my life, break, in the name of Jesus.</item>
        <item>My sun shall shine, in the name of Jesus.</item>
        <item>Let every financial failure in my life receive permanent termination in the name of Jesus.</item>
        <item>Every curse pronounced inwardly against my destiny, break, in the name of Jesus.</item>
        <item>O God arise and begin to disgrace all my Goliaths, in the name of Jesus.</item>
        <item>I command every sickness on my way to convert to divine health for me, in Jesus name.</item>
        <item>Father Lord, use all the people in my environment to bless me and let anointing of prosperity fall on me, in the name of Jesus.</item>
        <item>In Jesus mighty name, I fire back every arrow, spiritual bullets and satanic missiles fired at me.</item>
        <item>Every spirit of limitation against my breakthroughs, die, in the name of Jesus.</item>
        <item>I bind every spirit of frustration, defeat, delayed blessing and fear in my environment, in the name of Jesus.</item>
        <item>Every power of demotion targeted against my destiny, die, in the name of Jesus.</item>
        <item>O Lord, soak me in the spirit of prayer</item>
        <item>Every spirit, power and personality working against my elevation, die, in the name of Jesus.</item>
        <item>Lord, get all my stubborn pursuers occupied with unprofitable assignments, in the name of Jesus.</item>
        <item>Let God arise in His anger and fight for me.</item>
        <item>Thank God for His love, and mercy on you.</item>


    </string-array>
</resources>